<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[iDlife]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[iDlife]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/idlife/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 03:41:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/idlife/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Take Your Free Assessment Now!  |   Join IDLife   |   Login  Home Products IDTransformation The Opportunity The Team Questions Events   Weightloss Challenge Fit Challenge Performance Challenge Your IDT Calendar Watch The Video Buy Now           Base Kit     TAKE THE CHALLENGE   After reviewing the comprehensive IDLife product line, the most asked question is, “Where do I start?” IDLife has the answer to your question. Introducing the 28-Day IDTransformation. You choose the flavor combinations and our team will put together your personalized kit that combines the very best protein shakes in the industry, with a natural weight management product that provides a boost to your metabolism and supports the preservation of your lean muscle mass, and an energy product that can give you the immediate boost that you need along with a sustained energy to keep you going throughout the day. When combined with your IDNutrition, you now have the total foundation needed to help you achieve all of your health and wellness goals.*     Buy Now                        Now that you have made the choice to take The Challenge and transform your body, IDLife wants to make sure that you have the tools and resources to complement the unmatched nutritional products contained within the program. IDWellness is a HIPAA compliant online/mobile resource that allows you to set goals, track your nutrition and fitness progress, educate yourself on every aspect of health and wellness, and get a snap shot of the current state of your health. The best part is that this is all included as part of your IDTransformation package at no additional cost! You’ve made the decision to transform; now you have a state-of-the-art tool that will track your progress and results.     TOOLS AND RESOURCES      IDLIFE APP  IDWELLNESS PROGRAM  YOUR IDT CALENDAR  28 DAY GUIDE       DESIGN YOUR CHALLENGE     Learn more Learn more Learn more         SUCCESS STORIES                           WIN $500 EVERY MONTH   Nothing is more rewarding than seeing the results of hard work and dedication to a desired goal. At IDLife we want to recognize and reward those achievements and share them with the world. To do this, we have developed our My Story campaign that financially rewards people every month, simply by sharing their stories of transformation. To participate, simply take your before and after photos and send them, along your submission paperwork to mystory@idlife.com. Who knows, you might just be our next monthly winner!     SUBMIT NOW                              THE FOUNDATION OF HEALTH AND WELLNESS   Though not included in the IDTransformation Kit, IDNutrition is the foundation on which the IDTransformation is built. This one-of-a-kind nutritional supplement program takes all the guesswork out of what you need and delivers your truly personalized pharmaceutical grade nutrition, with your name on it, directly to your door.  IDNutrition recommends what you need, leaves out what you don’t and blocks things known to the system to have a possible adverse effect based on the answers you provide. The result is a program that is revolutionizing the health and wellness industry.     TAKE THE ASSESSMENT               Results may vary. Exercise and proper diet are necessary to achieve and maintain weight loss and muscle definition. Consult your physician and follow all safety instructions before beginning any exercise program or using any supplement or nutritional product. The information on our websites are not intended to diagnose or treat and medical condition or to replace the advice of a healthcare professional.   These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease.   * IDLife does not represent that its products are certified organic under the United States Department of Agriculture rules and regulations.         Login IDLife Products IDNutrition IDLife Weight Management IDLife Energy IDLife Sleep IDLife Opportunity Compensation Plan IDLife Team Meet The Team Questions IDNutrition FAQ Health Assessment FAQ Weight Management FAQ Connect Contact Us Events IDLife Blog Facebook Twitter Instagram Pinterest YouTube Copyright 2015 ID Life LLC. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy  Terms of Use  DSA Code of Ethics</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://dtieff.idlife.com/idtransformation/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">263cd9a7-7e92-4b47-b4e4-2031e3e4031f</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 03:40:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Welcome </h1><p>Every Person Is Unique!
We’ve taken the guess work out of finding which vitamins are right for you! Highest quality nutrients, dosages, and formulas supported by clinical studies. Superior Value at up to 40% less than retail.

IMG_1118.JPG
Using intensive cutting-edge research, we develop and sell industry-leading custom vitamin programs and products using the latest advancements in nutritional science, clinical research, and pharmaceutical-grade nutrients. Our proprietary formulas feature an exclusive ID Nutrition AM and PM pak system to ensure that the right nutrient is delivered when the body needs it most. To provide maximum safety we also screen for negative drug and nutrient interactions to ensure the best possible health outcomes.

How We Do It:
Through our clinical and evidence-based nutritional products, backed by thousands of scientific studies, we are able to zero-in on your individual needs and goals to deliver highly targeted vitamin recommendations. Each nutrient and clinically proven dosage is selected to address your specific nutritional gaps, lifestyle and medication therapy support.

The ID Nutrition Difference:
•Patented on-line health assessment process providing 100% personalized results.
•Clinically driven nutrient and dose recommendations.
•Safety screened for drug, nutrient and allergy interactions.
•Convenient, effective AM and PM dosing paks to maximize absorption.
•Added Bio-active compounds to enhance antioxidant delivery.

4 Steps:
1. Take the Free Personal Health Assessement (Only takes about 10 minutes)
2. We design a person nutrient program just for you (Based on the lastest medical science)
3. Review your supplement program and order (Your supplements will arrive within 1 week)
4. Start on the road to better health (Enjoy more energy, better sleep, a stronger immune system and reach your goals.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/idlife/welcome/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b95b7e17-3551-4b56-b485-283f39814e61</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 03:20:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>,,,,,</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/idlife/b03c70ed-33b6-4ece-8207-71f8d5fe3370/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b03c70ed-33b6-4ece-8207-71f8d5fe3370</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 03:40:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>